Tableau can connect to many data sources.
Tableau 可以连接多个数据源
You will notice here in the connect pane,
注意这里的“连接”(Connect) 窗格
we have a long list of connections to all sorts of data sources.
窗格中有一长串的列表 可以连接各种数据源
Whether it's local files,
不论是本地文件
databases on premises or in the cloud.
还是云端部署的数据库（都可以连接）
If you're using Tableau public you'll see fewer source options.
如果你用的是 Tableau Public 那么数据源的选项会少一些
Today we'll be using the global superstore
今天我们要用的是 "Global Superstore" Excel 文件
Excel file which you can find in the lesson resources.
你可以在课程资源中找到这个 Excel 文件
Superstore is a data set of sales for a global retail chain that sells furniture,
Superstore 是一个全球零售连锁的销售数据集
office supplies and technology goods.
包括家具、办公用品和科技产品的销售数据
Each row of data represents a single item in a transaction.
每行数据表示一个交易单项
To connect to the superstore file and Tableau,
要把 Superstore 文件连接 Tableau
click on Excel and navigate to where you download the file.
只要单击 "Excel" 选项 找到下载文件的位置
Now you see the data source page.
现在你看到“数据源”(Data Source) 页面了
On the left you can see all the sheets in the Excel file.
你会发现 Excel 中的所有工作表都在左边
Sheets in Excel are treated the same as tables in the database.
Excel 的工作表等同于数据库中的表格
And we can choose to connect to a single table or join multiple tables.
我们可以选择连接单个或多个表格
Simply drag a sheet onto the canvas.
只要把表拖到“画布”(Cavas) 上
Tables can be renamed simply by double clicking on
双击表格名称可以对它重命名
the name and we can see the data down here in the grid.
数据就显示在下面的网格中了
There's a lot we can do on the screen.
我们可以在这个网格中做很多事情
For example, we can rename variables by double clicking on the titles.
比如 双击标题对变量重命名
We can change the variable types by clicking on this icon here.
单击这个图标更改变量类型
And there's a drop down for more advanced options.
单击下拉图标会展开更多高级选项
A workbook can have multiple data sources.
一个工作簿可以对应多个数据源
If you click add here you can add another data source as a cross database join.
如果你单击这里的 “添加”(Add)  你可以跨数据库连接另一个数据源
If you want to add another data source entirely,
如果想单独连接另一个数据源
you can go up here to data.
你可以往上找到 "数据"(Data)
New data source. This will allow you to
（点击下拉列表中的）“新建数据源”(New Data Source) 这将允许你
access multiple data sources as you're creating your visualizations.
在创建可视化图表时访问多个数据源